[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following color of egg is incorrect for a chicken egg?", "correct_answer": "black", "incorrect_answers": ["white", "pink", "blue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Chinese astrology, why is it considered to be a poor match, if your partner is six years older or younger than you?", "correct_answer": "The signs are directly opposite each other.", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "The signs are not a part of a perfect triangle creating balance.", "The years you were born in are represented by the same animal."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Superman Returns, Lois Lane is married to Superman.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of Abigails collections does Ben Gates contribute to in the movie National Treasure?", "correct_answer": "Coin shaped pin", "incorrect_answers": ["Stamp", "Key chain", "Scroll"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This oil is said to be the richest natural source of vitamin E. It is widely used in cosmetics as an anti-ageing substance.", "correct_answer": "Wheat germ oil", "incorrect_answers": ["Olive oil", "Palm oil", "Sunflower oil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first movie in color to win the Best Picture Academy Award?", "correct_answer": "Gone with the Wind", "incorrect_answers": ["The Wizard of Oz", "The Color Purple", "Singin in the Rain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What world-famous female model was born on February 28, 1984?", "correct_answer": "Karolina Kurkova", "incorrect_answers": ["Gisele B\u00fcndchen", "Natalia Vodianova", "Adriana Lima"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which one of these sciences is the TOE theory studied?", "correct_answer": "Physics", "incorrect_answers": ["Paleontology", "Philosophy", "Biophysics"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Smokeys Mexican friend in the film Friday?", "correct_answer": "Hector", "incorrect_answers": ["Jesus", "Mario", "Pierre"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Carlton Magee invented this often-hated device.", "correct_answer": "The parking meter", "incorrect_answers": ["The police siren", "The income tax short form", "The traffic light"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country is the popular Spice cake believed to have originated?", "correct_answer": "the United States", "incorrect_answers": ["Brazil", "France", "Philippines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do we call cells with a nucleus?", "correct_answer": "Eukaryotic", "incorrect_answers": ["Mitochondrial", "Golgi", "Prokaryotic"]}]